There are three common techniques you can use to gather additional
有三个常用的技巧 可用于采集
data about your users.
用户附加数据
They vary along two major axes.
它们随两个主轴变化
Some give more in-depth customized data.
有些给出了更深度自定义的数据
But others will be possible to run on a greater total number of participants.
有些可能需要更大的参与人数
The first is called user experience research, or UER.
第一个称为用户体验研究 或 UER
Here, you can go really deep with just a few users,
你只需要对几个用户进行深入研究
often by observing them doing tasks of interest,
通常通过观察他们执行感兴趣的任务
like taking a lesson of a course as well as asking them questions.
如参加一堂课 并问他们一些问题
You get a lot of detailed and in-depth information that is useful primarily for
你获得了很多详细、深入的信息
brainstorming ideas, anything from coming up with ideas to changes to
对头脑风暴非常有用 从提出想法到对测试进行修改
tests, to identifying problems with your user experience in a way that you can
到通过转化为可用于评估
translate into a possible metric that you could use to evaluate your A/B test.
A/B 测试指标的方式来发现用户体验问题
You can also use special equipment in a UER
你还可以在用户体验研究中使用特殊实验
to get information that you couldn't get from your site's data.
得到你无法从你的网站数据中得到的信息
For example, you could use a special camera that tracks eye movement
例如 你可以使用一个能够跟踪眼球运动的特殊相机
to see what users are looking at, even if they don't click or
查看用户在看什么 即使他们不点击或
otherwise interact with the page.
与网页互动
However, you'll want to make sure that you validate the results of a UER with
然而 你可以采用
something like the retrospective analyses Carrie talked about.
Carrie 谈到的回顾性分析方法 对用户体验研究结果进行验证
The second method is called focus groups.
第二个方法是焦点小组访谈
With focus groups, you bring a bunch of users or potential users together for
在这个方法中 你可以将一群用户或潜在用户组织在一起
a group discussion.
进行群组讨论
You can talk to more total users than with a UER study, but
你可以和比用户体验研究更多的用户交流
you can't go as deep with each person.
但却不能和每个人深入交流
Once you bring the users together, you could show them screen shots or
将用户组织在一起以后 可以向他们展示截图
images, you could walk them through a demo, and
或图片 可以进行演示
then you can ask them questions to elicit feedback.
然后你可以问他们问题 从而引出反馈
You can also often ask hypothetical questions, but
你还可以经常问一些假设性问题
even if you have a skilled facilitator, you run the risk of group think and
但即使你有一个得力的协调人员 也会有群体思维和
convergence on fewer opinions.
意见减少的风险
Have you ever been in a room and there's been a few loud voices that dominate?
你是否在一个具有一些不同声音的房间里待过？
That same dynamic can occur in focus groups.
在焦点小组内会发生相同的情况
Third, surveys are when you recruit a population and
第三 调查是你招募到一群人 然后
ask them a bunch of questions, either online, or in person, or via telephone.
在线或面对面或通过电话问他们一些问题
Surveys are pretty cheap to run on a whole bunch of users, and
对一群用户进行调查的成本很低
the data you get is much more quantitative, but it's not very deep or
而且得到的数据更具量化性 但深度不够
individually customized.
或不具有个体自定义性
Surveys are useful for gathering metrics that you cannot directly measure
调查对于采集自己不能直接测量的指标非常有用
yourself, such as the question about how many students who take audacity
如有多少学习过 Audacity 课程的学员找到了工作
classes get jobs, how productive they are at their job, and
他们在工作中表现如何
whether the classes contributed to their success.
以及课程对其成功是否有帮助等
That said, be careful with survey results.
但是要小心对待调查结果
Users don't have to tell the truth, and
用户不一定会说实话
their answers can be dependent on how the questions are phrased.
他们的答案可能取决于如何描述问题
Because of this, you can almost never directly compare survey results
因此 不能直接将调查结果
to results computed using more observational methods.
和使用观察性方法计算的结果进行比较
There are more details about these methods,
关于这些方法
as well as some other techniques, in the PDF linked in the instructor's notes.
和其他一些技巧 在讲师注释中链接的 PDF 中有详细说明